videopoker.com 2004-04-12

# The casino and video poker player's world of action gaming

**Videopoker.com Privacy Statement**

We want to assure our registered members and visitors that we respect your privacy and understand that it is a great concern to many people. Videopoker.com will not willfully disclose any personally identifiable information of any member to any third party without the authorization of the member. Please read this Private Policy and it will explain the way we handle your personal information. If you have any questions pertaining to this policy or have any legal questions, please contact John Roethel at [**jer@jeroethel.com**](mailto:jer@jeroethel.com%20?Subject=Regarding%20videopoker.com).

**Privacy Policy Coverage**  
**·** · This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personal identifiable information Videopoker.com collects when you are on the videopoker.com site, and when you use any of our services. 

**·** · This policy also covers videopoker.com's treatment of any personal identifiable information that videopoker.com's business partners share with videopoker.com . This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that videopoker.com does not control, or to people that videopoker.com does not employ or manage.

**Information Collection and Use**  
When you register with videopoker.com, we ask for your name, email address, age, address, zip code, occupation, industry, or another other information needed for registration purposes. Once you register with us, and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

Videopoker.com may use your personal information towards our marketing effort only if you choose the option to when you register with us. 

Videopoker.com uses your personal information for three general purposes: 

· To track your interest so that we can target our web site towards your interests.   
· To fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and   
· To contact you about specials and new products. 

The information we gather or collect through membership registration, entries to promotion or sweepstakes on videopoker.com will not be sold to any third parties. 

Videopoker.com may also receive and share personally identifiable information with our business partners affiliated with us in order to put forth marketing effort.

Videopoker.com also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
Videopoker.com will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.

Videopoker.com will only send personal identifiable information about you to other companies or people with the following exceptions:

· We have your consent to share the information; we need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;   
· We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of videopoker.com to provide a product or service to you. (These companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.);   
· We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or   
· We find that your actions on our web sites violate the videopoker.com terms or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services. 

**Security of Your Account**  
Account information is password-protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas videopoker.com uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy Action**  
Videopoker.com may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcements on our web site.

**Questions and Suggestions**  
Please direct your questions or suggestions to [**grogan@videopoker.com.**](mailto:grogan@videopoker.com)
